Yulianto Ardi Nugroho

Bandung, Indonesia | 085524687013 | yuliantoardin@gmail.com

Summary

A software developer enthusiast, have 2.5 years experience in the field of software development, intrested in web and hybrid mobile development using Javascript framework, experienced in Vue js, Git, Trello and testing apps. Successfully Digitalize process in Bank Indonesia, Best graduate of Informatic Engineering 2016 at Institut Teknologi Nasional Bandung. have experience in the field of Quality Assurance for application e-commerce

Experience

BANK INDONESIA – Jakarta, Indonesia

Software Engineer (2021-Juli 2023)

- Worked on development of DWP (Digital Workspace) for *Rapat Dewan Gubernur* (Board of Governors Meeting) digitalization needs, responsible for development Front End use Vue, with job detail:
 - o Convert design from figma to Vue quality code
 - Successfully deliver around 16 major feature in agile environment
 - Versioning control use Git
 - Collaborate with Back End in maintaining data security and seamless integration.
 - o Implement Bootstrap, vuetify, vuex, axios and Vue-router and other Vue Ecosystem
 - Maintain a responsive display and cross-browser support so the web can be accessed from various device and browser without any problem
- Worked on development of BIDIVE document management to fulfil the needs of *Gubernur Bank Indonesia* and *Rapat Dewan Gubernur*(Board of Governors Meeting), responsible for development Front End using Vue and custom webpart Sharepoint, with job detail:
 - o Integrate Front End with Rest Api and Odata from Sharepoint onPremise
 - o Successfully deliver around 10 feature from document tree view, sorting and filtering to user management
 - o Participating in design and testing of the web
 - Develop web to support mobile view including ipad and smartphone
- Develop, deploy and maintenance tools IGOV metadata management for bank report Antasena using VB.Net, with iob detail:
 - Develop add-in excel tools for front end and back-end using to communicate with SQL Server using VB.net and hosting both in IIS environment
 - o Maintenance, handle bug, gather user requirement, analysis and design solution for user
 - Successfully develop user need and enhance IGOV performance 10x

PT SETIAP HARI DIPAKAI (EVERMOS) - Bandung, Indonesia

Intern Quality Assurance (2019 –2020)

- · Conduct discussion regarding the flow testing and creating test case based on new feature that will be developed
- Search, reproduce and report bug that happens to the user regarding the application
- Conduct testing in terms of security and functionality of new or existing features in the application
- Make automated test for Evermos android apps using espresso automation testing and selenium for Evermos web

Education

Institut Teknologi Nasional – Bandung, Indonesia (2016 – 2020)

S1 Informatic Engineering – best graduate of Informatic Engineering IPK 3,92

Certification & Training

Pelatihan Back End Web API Programming	2020
Javascript course Udemy	2023
Css Course Udemy	2023
Vue Course Udemy	2023

Additional

Skills : HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, SCSS, Javascript, Vue JS, GIT, Rest Api, SQL, MSSQL, VB.Net

Tools: VS Code, Visual Studio, Postman, Github Desktop, IIS Server

Soft skill: Willingness to learn, Time management, Hardworker, Patience, Communication, Problem solving, Curiosity